Xian-Hao (Harry) Liao

xliao1737@massart.edu Boston, MA +1(857)-693-8315 https://blogs.massart.edu/xianhaoliao

Creative professional with 3+ years of experience in website development, designing layouts for promotional materials, and utilizing 3D modeling skills for prototyping. In 2023, I completed my UX Design Professional Certificate from Google, and now work as a Web Archivist at MassArt.

Work Experience

MassArt / Graduate Assistantship

09/2022 - 05/2024, Boston, MA, U.S.

At MassArt, I managed the DMI program website, spearheading a rebranding project that enhanced the interface and user experience. Key achievements include a 20% increase in user engagement, 30% faster page load times, and a 25% rise in user satisfaction after the redesign.

BJ's Wholesale Club / Creative Design Internship

05/2023 - 08/2023, Marlborough, MA, U.S.

Interned at BJ's Wholesale Club Creative Design, where I created social motion graphics, increasing engagement by 40%, and designed marketing materials that enhanced brand identity, leading to a 15% uptick in campaign response rates.

Future House Music / 3D Artist

05/2021 - 07/2022, Amsterdam, Netherlands, Remote

Design and adjustment the 3D Scene by using C4D. Discuss back and forth with clients to finalize artwork. Released on Spotify, and YouTube with 10K+ views and 1K+ subscribers.

ABC Design / Graphic Designer

07/2021 - 05/2022, Taichung City, Taiwan

Represent ABC Design.de's products in Taiwan. Rolled out new product ideas including social media engagements and marketing materials which launched to over 150 local retail stores. Facilitated cross-departmental work and served as the go-to person of the design department. Coordinated with suppliers on material decisions and color corrections to support new product launches.

Bonneboutique Shop / Product Photographer

03/2019 - 06/2020, Taichung City, Taiwan

Co-led the design and development of a new online store launched in July 2019. Conducted professional photoshoots, including scene preparations for products in the online store. Ran promotional events on social media and increased sales amount by 20%.

Education

MassArt / MFA DMI

Massachusetts College of Art and Design Master of Fine Arts, Dynamic Media Institute

MIT / Cross-regist at Media Lab

Massachusetts Institute of Technology Cross Registration at Media Arts and Science

NTCUST / BA CD

National Taichung University of Science and Technology Bachelor of Design, Commercial Design

Technical Expertise

Design: Adobe Illustrator, Cinema 4D, Octane Render, Photoshop, Indesign, Lightroom, Capture one

Visual Production: Adobe Premiere, After Effect, Final cut pro, Ableton Live, AVID Pro Tools, AVID Composer

Prototyping: Adobe XD, Figma, UI/UX, interactive flow with HTML/ CSS/ JS, Bootstrap, WordPress.org

Design Projects

Cocook Mobile Application Prototypes Lead Designer, 05/2023 - 09/2023

Lucky App AI Chatbot Prototypes

Main Developer, 09/2022 - 01/2023

Abc design X Sunny Wang 2021 Comercial Visual Designer, 01/2020 - 06/2020

C-Cube Information Architecture Design

Team Leader, 01/2020 - 06/2020